Key to proper writing:

Be result oriented in your narratives, state facts in percentages, and relative percentages as often as you can .

Questions

Results

Validation

	●	What, precisely, was your contribution?
	•	What question did you answer?
	•	Why should the reader care?
	•	What larger question does this address?
	●	What is your new result?
	•	What new knowledge have you contributed that the reader can use elsewhere?
	•	What previous work (yours or someone else’s) do you build on? What do you provide a superior alternative to?
	•	How is your result different from and better than this prior work?
	•	What, precisely and in detail, is your new result?
	●	Why should the reader believe your result?
	•	What standard should be used to evaluate your claim?
	•	What concrete evidence shows that your result satisfies your claim?
